Branden Daniel Ng

Front-End Web Developer Melbourne, VIC

linkedin.com/in/brandendaniel in github.com/BrandenDaniel 😱

Web Portfolio - branden.vercel.app

J 04 32 375 587

Experienced front-end web developer with a fiery passion for transforming static wireframes into interactive, beautiful spaced websites. Throughout my journey, I've had the privilege to collaborate with a diverse range of clients and businesses. I am currently learning React.js and API integrations.

Work Experience

LeasePLUS Group - SafeCode

Sept. 2022 - Present Melbourne CBD, VIC

Apr. 2022 - Sept. 2022

Sept. 2019 - Feb. 2020

Melbourne CBD, VIC

Melbourne CBD. VIC

Front-end Web Developer

SafeCode, a LeasePLUS subsidiary, creates novated leasing and salary packaging interfaces for individuals and businesses. With 100,000+ users, they cater to diverse clients across Australia.

- Worked on proprietary leasing/salary packaging software for LeasePlus Group
- Management of all LeasePlus group's websites/portals (over 5+)

LeasePLUS Group - SalaryPackagingPLUS

Accounts Officer - salary deductions receivable & payable

Arcadian Digital &

Junior Front-end Web Developer

As a bespoke digital and marketing agency, Arcadian deliver tailored solutions to organisations of all sizes. I worked with extremely talented engineers during my time there.

- Collaborative work with project managers and lead/senior developers
- · Build and structure WordPress child themes
- Build and maintan the company's own WordPress plugins and themes

Bebble Media &

May. 2018 - Jun. 2019 North Laverton, VIC

Junior Front-end Web Developer

A small digital agency in West Melbourne with in-house designers and developers. Specialising in WordPress, they assist small business owners in expanding their ecommerce and online presence.

- Collaborate with web/graphic designers to reach mockup standards
- Integrations of plugins + customisation of plugins to suit client's specifics
- · Manipulation of software styles (i.e plugins, themes) exact to design mockups

Tech Stack & Skills Interests & Hobbies

HTML JavaScript React **CSS** Sass Git jQuery Bootstrap **API** integration ETFs & Index Funds Personal Finance Tech Critically Acclaimed Films Youtube

Work

2022

2019

MySalPack (employee portal) & 2023 My Web Portfolio &

JavaScript, ¡Query, Sass, Blazor, Bootstrap MySalPack (employer portal) &

React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS (Sass)

Personal Projects

Cryptoverse &

JavaScript, ¡Query, Sass, Blazor, Bootstrap

YouTube Clone &

React, Material UI, Rapid API, Axios, Sass

Print Strategy Management @ JavaScript, jQuery, WordPress, Bootstrap, CSS

React, Redux, Rapid API, Axios, Sass, Ant Design

Education

Udacity Front End Web Developer Nanodegree

Online Oct. 2017 - May 2018

Team Treehouse

Online

2023

2023

2023

Front End Web Development Track

May - Aug. 2017

RMIT University

Melbourne, VIC

Completed 48 credits towards a Bachelor of Information Technology

Jul. 2016 - Apr. 2017

- Relevant Courses Included:
- Web Programming
- · User-centered Design